Palisha Tuladhar

Mobile (+66) 949940842 • E-MAIL palishat@gmail.com • Skype ID tpalisha



OBJECTIVE

To succeed in an environment of diversity, growth and excellence, which provides self-development and help achieve organizational as well as personal goals

PROFILE

Experience in Recruitment, Marketing, PR and Business Development 1 year exposure in Recruitment Industry 2 years of exposure in Airline Industry Dedicated, highly motivated, extrovert and a team player Effective negotiation, problem solving and interpersonal skills Proficiency in Microsoft Word, Excel, SPSS, PowerPoint and Amadeus Fluent in English, Hindi, Nepali and Thai (Intermediate)

EXPERIENCE

ADI Resourcing Co., Ltd, Business Development / Recruitment Consultant

Bangkok, Thailand (Feb 2015 - Present)

- Responsible for developing foreign/local clients & candidates through various marketing (online/offline) channels
- Developing a good understanding of client's respective industry, their requirements, their work culture & environment to identify right fit candidate
- Attracting, informing and sourcing candidates through various tools such as social media, professional outreach, referral campaigns, research, official websites, career exhibitions, networking events, E-newsletters, universities programs and workshop
- Handling end to end recruitment/outsourcing process for junior to senior level roles (IT/Non IT)
- Coordinating and following up with clients and candidates to ensure smooth transition of candiate in the new workplace
- Coordinating and supporting sales team & recruitment team to improve operational process
- Driving the sales/ recruitment team to achieve quarterly targets
- Identifying the potential target groups, market competitors, market landscape analysis and projecting the market opportunities
- Conducting competitors analysis by keeping abreast of marketing trends and competitor moves, to improve presence in overall market
- Monitoring and analyzing the campaigns performance and generating reports
- Assisting in ad-hoc projects to support growing business

Kim Pai Thai O.P.P Public Co., Ltd, Internship

Bangkok, Thailand (May 2014 – July 2014)

Human Resource Recruitment Assistant

- Published company job vacancies through various online channels and created database of candidate for various positions and placed them for interviews
- Coordinated end to end recruitment and supported orientation program
- Organized and supported English for Business training and workshop for the company employees

Marketing and Overseas Purchasing Assistant

- Executed market research on Plastic Packaging in ASEAN market
- Negotiated via online communication with overseas suppliers and selected quality vendors after it passed the company's quality standard
- Procurement of plastic films, to meet order placement by clients and worked closely with sales team on the requirement of the raw materials for packaging & labeling
- Tracked vendor performances and maintained relationship with the vendors

Qatar Airways, Senior PR & Marketing Assistant

Kathmandu, Nepal (April 2011- Feb 2013)

- Initiated, developed and managed all marketing strategies, plans and communications as well as evaluated the result after the implementation
- Allocated yearly budget for the station and maintained budget expenditure reports to track cost effective marketing spend
- Reviewed annual business report in order to set up yearly marketing plan and strategies by understanding the market dynamics and requirements to meet the incremental target of the station
- Accountable for starting up country dedicated website and updated the website with special tactical fares, seasonal promotions, campaigns and responsible for the content of the website
- Executed digital marketing activities such as online advertisements, Google Adwords, social media campaigns, radio & TV commercials to meet and exceed the online revenue target for the station
- Analyzed performance of each online/offline marketing paid channels and made critical decision to optimize spending and provided recommendations for improvement
- Planned and organized corporate & trade partner recognition events such as Award Night, Product Introduction Workshop, Familiarization Trip and Ambassador's /Corporate Dinner.

- Implemented acquisition and retention strategies for Frequent Flyers
 Members and to increase active member base for each tier
- Built and maintained media relationship and corresponded for press release and organized press meet
- Decided on partnership activities and sponsorship, which would enhance the brand name and visibility
- Executed Corporate Social Responsibility activities
- Coordinated and supported Qatar Airways Recruitment Drive 2013 in Nepal
- Managed any ad-hoc project in coordination with head office marketing team and other departments

Qatar Airways, Temporary Executive Assistant

(December 2010 - February 2011)

- Arranged and coordinated office meetings and conferences
- Reviewed and summarized miscellaneous reports and documents
- Prepared documents and outgoing mails
- Coordinated and arranged travel schedule and reservations

EDUCATION

Asian Institute of Technology, Bangkok, Thailand (Jan 2013 – Dec 2014) Masters in Business Administration (MBA)

Major: Marketing and Human Resource - CGPA: 3.59

Assumption University, Bangkok, Thailand (May 2007- Oct 2010) Bachelors in Business Administration (BBA)

Major: International Business Management (IBM) - CGPA: 3.29

Mayo College Girls' School, Ajmer, India (March 1999-May 2007) Indian School Certificate Examination 2007

COURSES & TRAININGS

- E-commerce Induction, Qatar Airways Doha (17th 20th September 2012)
- Competitive Strategies for a Global Marketplace Course, Qatar Airways (21st August 2012)
- Transitioning into a Project Management Role Course, Qatar Airways (21st August 2012)
- Manage Project Course, Qatar Airways (07th August 2012)
- Troubleshooting and Closing the Project Course, Qatar Airways (29th June 2012)
- Initiating and Planning a Project Course, Qatar Airways (07th June 2012)
- Project Management Fundamentals Course, Qatar Airways (24th May 2012)

- Interpersonal Communication Course, Communicating with Confidence, Qatar Airways (21st May 2012)
- Influencing with Impact Course Training, Qatar Airways Doha (14th -15th May 2012)
- 5- Star on the Ground- Internal Customer Course Training, Qatar Airways Doha (05th -06th March 2012)
- Time & Priority Management Course Training, Qatar Airways Doha (20th -21st Feb 2012)
- Basic Amadeus Course Training, Qatar Airways Kathmandu (11th -15th July, 2011)

ACADEMIC ACHIVEMENTS

- Academic Honor Reward (May2007-2008)
- The Rector's Certificate of Honors (2007- 2008)

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Title of Competent Communicator, Toastmasters International (Sept, 2010)
- Representative of Assumption University. Cross-Cultural Program. Bangkok Sister Youth Program 2010(1st-9thJuly 2010)
- Vice President of Membership, Assumption University Toastmasters Club (2007-2009)
- Representative of Nepal for the Exhibition and Promotion of Culture in the International Week 2008 (November 25-27th 2008)
- Organized an official Inaugural Meeting, New Membership Orientation and Speech Contest for Assumption University Toastmasters Club (2008)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Gender: FemaleNationality: Nepalese

Date of Birth: 24-08-1988

REFEREES

Mr. Ramdas Shivram

Country Manager, Qatar Airways – Indonesia E-mail: rshivram@id.qatarairways.com

Prof. Dr. Ram Manohar Shrestha

Professor Emeritus at Asian Institute of Technology (AIT)-Thailand Senior Research Analyst for Energy Economics and Planning

E-mail: ram.m.shrestha@gmail.com